ecorazzi.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy | ecorazzi.com :: the latest in green gossip

Last modified December 18, 2009

Ecorazzi.com (“Ecorazzi”, “we” or “us”) respects your privacy and has adopted policies and procedures for ensuring that it’s users’ (you) personal information is handled responsibly as described below.

### Information Collection

Ecorazzi collects information from the website’s visitors at several different points:

**Browsing**  
Users may browse Ecorazzi, subject to our website [Terms of Service](http://www.ecorazzi.com/terms), without providing any individually identifiable information.

**Registration**  
Users must register in order to use certain features of Ecorazzi, such as the mailing list. During registration visitors are required to provide contact information such as name, email and mailing address. Ecorazzi uses this information to contact visitors about features and services that we believe may be of interest. Registration data may also include demographic information (such as gender or age) and subject matter preferences so that Ecorazzi can effectively tailor editorial content according to interest.

**Requests and Orders**  
When a visitor contacts Ecorazzi, we request contact information to enable us to deliver the respond, such as name, email address, phone number, and mailing address and, if applicable, financial, payment, or billing information.

**Links**  
We offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours.

### Information Use

**Profile**  
Each time users visit Ecorazzi, we receive basic technical information from your computer, including your Internet protocol (IP) address, domain name, referral data (e.g., the address of the website you visited before clicking through to our website), and browser and platform type. We store this technical information using cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our visitors. A profile consists of stored technical information that we keep on individual visitors that details their viewing preferences. These profiles do not contain information that identifies any visitor as an individual person. This information is used to provide offers and improve the content of the site for a visitor, and may be used to customize portions of our website for a visitor or direct certain types of information to a visitor. We may share profile information (without individually identifying information) with third parties.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file stored on a visitor’s computer that contains information about the visitor. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies to keep track of the traffic in the website. For the session ID cookie, once visitors close the browser, the cookie simply terminates and is not retained. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the visitor’s hard drive for an extended period of time and help us target the interests of the users so we can enhance the visitor’s future experience. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

If visitors decline to accept cookies, they may still access Ecorazzi, but some portions of our site may be inaccessible or slower to access.

Ecorazzi uses third party advertising companies to serve ads on our website.  Some of them may use DART cookies or other cookies to enable them to better serve ads based on the users’ interests (by their visits to Ecorazzi and/or other websites).

Users can opt out the use of the DART cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Users can opt out of some, but not all, of third party cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Log Files**  
Ecorazzi uses log files to track visitors’ access to our website. This includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**  
Ecorazzi employs software technology called “clear gifs” (also known as “web beacons” or “web bugs”) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is most popular and most effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of website visitors. Clear gifs are invisible on the page and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to visitors’ personally identifiable information.

### Communication from Ecorazzi

**Ecorazzi by Email**  
If a visitor wishes to subscribe to Ecorazzi’s Email newsletter, we must collect registration information including the visitor’s name and email address. Subscribers may unsubscribe to stop receiving these email communications.

**Announcements**  
Ecorazzi occasionally emails registered visitors about new features, promotions, events, or other information that may be of interest to them.

**Customer Service**  
If we need to communicate with back with a registered visitor, we generally use email, but may use other methods of communication as appropriate, if the visitor supplies such information to us.

### Sharing of Information

**Legal Requirements**  
Although we make every effort to preserve visitor privacy, we may need to disclose personal information as required by law or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding or a court order or legal process served on us, or to assert or defend our legal rights, or to protect us or others from harm to persons or property.

**Public Postings**  
Ecorazzi provides opportunities for visitors to express their opinions and views in accordance with the standards of conduct in our [Terms of Service](http://www.ecorazzi.com/terms). Visitors submit information to these forums with the understanding that the information will be made publicly available.  
**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Ecorazzi’s visitors are given the opportunity to “opt out” of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information.  
**Surveys, Sweepstakes & Contests**  
We occasionally conduct surveys, sweepstakes, or contests. Participation in these is completely voluntary and visitors have a choice of whether to disclose personally identifiable information in order to take part. Contact information will be shared with the survey, sweepstakes, or contest sponsors or used by Ecorazzi internally to notify the winners and award prizes.

### **Contact Information**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please send an email to info@ecorazzi.com or call  (305) 747-1411 .
